Finding Aid for the In the Life records LSC.2178
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Publicity and Press materials, (1991-2012; undated)
  - Splashlight Studios, undated (Box 55)
    Press materials for photographic studio space.
  - Straight Plan For The Gay Man, 2004 Feb 23 (Box 53)
    Clipping re: television program.
  - Sundance, 2004 (Box 54)
    Press materials for Sundance channel films.
  - Superstar In A Housedress, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
    Press kit and articles for documentary film.
  - That's A Family, 2002 (Box 53)
    Discussion and teaching guide for film.
  - Three Of Hearts, 2004 (Box 53)
  - TLA Entertainment Group, 2002 (Box 53)
  - Tong ZHI, 2000-2001 (Box 53)
    Press release, brochure, and articles referencing exhibit at Museum of Chinese in the Americas.
  - Touch Of Pink, 2004 July 16 (Box 53)
    Clipping referencing film.
  - Trans America, 2005 (Box 53)
    Press notes for film.
  - Transfigured Body (The), 2003 (Box 53)
    Press release and letter regarding multi-media performance piece.
  - Trembling Before G-d, 2001 (Box 53)
    Clipping referencing documentary film.
  - Tribeca, 2004 (Box 53)
    Press release for Tribeca Film Festival films.
  - True Colors, undated (Box 53)
    Publicity stills and synopsis for documentary film.
  - Two Brothers, 2004 Sep 24 (Box 53)
  - Venus Boyz, 2001 (Box 53)
  - Vermont, undated (Box 53)
    Blank postcards, featuring the state of Vermont.
  - W Hotels, undated (Box 55)
    Promotional catalog.
  - X - Stream Broadcasting, undated (Box 55)
    Press and notes for video streaming service.
- Development, Marketing, and Communications Files, (1991-2012, undated)
  The Development, Marketing, and Communications files consist of materials pertaining to branding, fundraising and development, and outreach. Includes documentation for In the Life benefits and special events as well as development and communications committees, strategic planning reports, and grant applications. There is no specific arrangement to this series.
  - 1995 Comments on ITL/Stations airing ITL (Box 57)
  - AD Buy, 2011 (Box 58)
    Invoices, email correspondence, and advertising rates for ITL.
  - Ad kits, budgets, rates, 2010 (Box 58)
  - Amazon Disc on Demand DVD Submission Guidelines and Createspace Content and Artwork Guide, undated (Box 58)
  - Another American Part II - benefit for ITL, 1999 (Box 66)
    Press and ticket sales for performance.
  - Anti-Defamation League (ADL), 2010 Aug 31 (Box 57)
    Correspondence requesting permission to use episode.
  - Blue State Digital (BSD) contract mark-Up, 2011 (Box 59)
    Website design consulting services agreement.
  - Chuy Sanchez Transition Documents/Priorities, 2009-2012 (Box 58)
    ITL Strategic Plan, itinerary for new hire, transition review, resume, interview questions.
  - CISION, 2010 (Box 57)
    Contract for media database service.
  - Corporate - Contacts List, Ideas, Miscellaneous (4 folders), 1991-2001 (Box 49)
    Contacts, lists of corporate sponsors, leads and potential funders,
  - Corporate Sponsorship notes, 2000-2001 (Box 50)
    Letters to potential corporate sponsors for ITL; notes with sponsor information and appointment dates.
  - Demographics, 1998-1999 (Box 50)
    ITL membership survey, results, and demographic profile. With articles referencing the gay and lesbian market.
  - Development Plan, 1997-2000 (Box 50)
    ITL development plan, event ideas, and brochures unrelated to ITL, referencing giving.
  - DVD and Video requests for ITL, ca. 2004-2006 (Box 67)
    Correspondence, invoices for ITL program requests.
  - Exciting New Technologies (ENT) agreement drafts and executed final, 2004-2005 (Box 49)
    Agreements between ITL and ENT for website design. With notes, instructions, plans, and email correspondence regarding website development.
  - Executive Program Services program packet, 2011 (Box 58)
    Press kit for syndication and free programming offers. With two DVDs.
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Screening: Ballroom, 2009 (Box 58)
    With surveys related to screening and ITL. Magazines with articles about HIV.
  - Guidelines for Talking to the Moveable Middle About LGBT Issues (Box 38)
    Report. Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
  - Haas Ads: Freedom to Marry, 2011 (Box 58)
    Email correspondence and invoices regarding ITL advertising campaign.
  - IFBP Pride Guide - The Life, 2009 (Box 57)
    Request for ITL to advertise in publication.
  - In the Life - metallic ephemera (Box 46)
    Metal stencil with ITL logo.
  - In the States: Florida, Ad Campaign, 2010 (Box 59)
    Advertising contracts.
  - ITL 2009-2010 Strategic Plan (Box 48)
  - ITL 2010 Rebranding (Box 59)
    Brand rollout schedule, internal memos, guidelines for logo and brand identity.
  - ITL 2010/11 Annual Reports (4 items), 2010-2011 (Box 48)
  - ITL Ad Budget: IN THE STATES: Florida, 2010 (Box 58)
    Budget, email correspondence, advertising rates.
  - ITL Arts Engine/Media That Matters: An Evening of Transgender Film and Video, undated (Box 58)
    Show run-down. With DVD.
  - ITL benefit invitations and correspondence, ca. 1990s-2003 (Box 67)
    With photographs on CD.
  - ITL benefits and special events (14 folders), ca. 1998-2007 (Box 66)
    Includes: Beautiful thing, Judy in June, Fabulous Story, Film Festival Laramie Project, Moon for Misbegotten, TV Dinners, South Beach Oscar Party, In the Life Pride Party, Pine's Party 2005, Major Donor Thank You Dinner, Special Events.
  - ITL Brand, 2010-2012 (Box 59)
    Marketing and communications guide, strategy proposal, social media best practices.
  - ITL Brand Brief, Community Relations Plan, 2006-2007 (Box 59)
  - ITL Communications Plan, 2011-2012 (Box 58)
    Renna Communications consulting agreement, timeline, talking points.
  - ITL Correspondence, 2011 (Box 46)
  - ITL Cross Promotion Strategy and press release, ca. 2009 (Box 59)
  - ITL Development meeting agenda, 2010 (Box 58)
    Agenda notes.
  - ITL Development/Communication meeting agenda notes, 2010-2011 (Box 58)
  - ITL Domain Name Registration, 2003-2004 (Box 49)
  - ITL Editorial Board meeting agendas, ca. 2010-2012 (Box 57)
  - ITL event invitations, 1995-1996, 1999, 2009, undated (Box 62)
  - ITL final grant-writing effort, 2010-2012 (Box 65)
    Foundation prospects, grant application, projected funding opportunities and resources.
  - ITL Follow-up Colorado contact information, 2011 (Box 59)
    Email with contact information.
  - ITL Gala 2009 (Box 58)
    Timeline, press release and speech.
  - ITL Gala 2010 (Box 58)
    Notes, media plan, sponsorship opportunities, show run-down.
  - ITL Grant Conference meeting agenda, 2010 Oct 7 (Box 58)
  - ITL information and membership brochure, 2001-2005 (Box 50)
    Brochure samples, mock-ups, correspondence, and cost estimates regarding brochure.
  - ITL Logo - rebranding, 2004 (Box 63)
  - ITL Mail, 2011-2012 (Box 59)
  - ITL Management team, 2012-2013 (Box 58)
  - ITL Member Letter Samples (Box 49)
    Sample letters re: ITL membership and support. Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
  - ITL Missions/Strategies/Master Narratives, ca. 2009-2012 (Box 59)
    Communications strategic plan, calendar, work plan, and job description for communications coordinator.
  - ITL MK (Michelle Kristel) weekly meeting notes, ca. 2010-2012 (Box 58)
    Agenda notes and email correspondence.
  - ITL National Branding Survey 2007 (Box 57)
  - ITL New Media meeting notes, undated (Box 57)
    Notes regarding promotions and resources.
  - ITL Newsletter and Annual Report hardcopies, 2008-2009; 2010-2011 (Box 59)
  - ITL Nielsen ratings statistics, ca. 1997-2000 (Box 50)
  - ITL Office Banner - Signed (Box 70)
  - ITL PR Interns, 2007 (Box 58)
    Internship description, email correspondence.
  - ITL Pride Brunch 2008 (Box 61)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Guest list, budget, correspondence, press, proof sheets, and photo disc.
  - ITL Pride Brunch letters and ephemera, 2011 (Box 59)
  - ITL Production/Communication meeting agenda notes, 2012 (Box 58)
  - ITL programming distribution, 2001-2002 (Box 67)
  - ITL Ratings, ca. 1993-2003 (Box 67)
    Ratings statistics and Research Reference Handbook.
  - ITL ratings statistics, 2006-2007 (Box 48)
  - ITL Rebranding Initiative and LGBT Media Survey, 2006-2007 (Box 49)
    Brand brief, correspondence, rebranding task force member list and LGBT media survey results
  - ITL Rebranding Survey 2007 (Box 48)
  - ITL Screening Surveys, undated (Box 59)
    Surveys for screening of Bullycide, and other unidentified screenings.
  - ITL Season Premier Galas 2008-2010 (4 folders) (Box 61)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Correspondence, press, invoices, facility contracts, insurance, and planning timelines. With photo discs.
  - ITL Season Premier Galas 2008-2010 (5 folders), 2008-2009 (Box 60)
  - ITL Staff Meetings: Materials and Agendas, 2010 (Box 58)
    Agenda notes, Executive Director work plans, staff priorities.
  - ITL stationary samples/logos, undated (Box 63)
  - ITL strategic plan, 2008 (Box 68)
  - ITL Strategic plan proposal and stakes, 2005 (Box 63)
  - ITL Strategic planning: consulting & notes, 2005 (Box 63)
  - ITL Transition Documents, 2010-2011 (Box 58)
    ITL new hire transition plan, communications coordinator work plan, communications calendar
  - ITL Website, 2007, 2012 (Box 58)
    Notes, email correspondence, website and YouTube statistics.
  - ITL Website redesign proposal, 2011 (Box 59)
  - ITL Website Survey Results, 2008 (Box 49)
    Survey responses regarding ITL website.
  - ITL: Corporate Funder Info Sheets (8 folders), ca. 2000 (Box 50)
    ITL press kit materials with fact sheets regarding ITL viewer responses, demographics, markets, and ratings, among others.
  - ITLM Gala 09, 2009 (Box 34)
  - ITLM Major Donor Q & A, undated (Box 49)
    Donor solicitation strategies.
  - LGBT Movement Communications Toolkit, 2008 (Box 56)
  - Marketing Concepts and Strategies (Box 47)
  - Media Contacts 2008, ca. 2006-2008 (Box 56)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Contact information for LGBT publications, editors, and publishers among others.
  - Movement Advancement Project (MAP) ITL Media report, 2007 (Box 49)
  - New York Times Screening - Bullycides, 2010 (Box 58)
    Press, email correspondence for screening of film produced by ITL.
  - Old ITL website info, 2004 (Box 63)
  - Out & Equal, undated (Box 57)
    Notes; appears related to specific ITL project.
  - PBS report - 1992 (Box 63)
    Report featuring publicity and press response for ITL.
  - Pride 2005 (Box 67)
    ITL logo and ad mock-ups for Pride 2005.
  - Pride Brunch 2009-2010 (2 folders) (Box 62)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Guest lists, gift reports, budget, contracts, press, correspondence, and planning timelines. With photo discs.
  - Requests for DVDs/Letters/Scanned Letters for In The Life Media, ca.1993-2005 (Box 46)
  - Strategic Plan Progress Report, 2009 Feb 12 (Box 57)
    Goals and strategies for ITL.
  - Summer of Stonewall, 2009 (Box 59)
    Fundraising and outreach campaign.
  - Thank you letters re: ITL programming, ca.1996-2005 (Box 46)
  - Youth Marketing Recommendation, 2006 (Box 56)
    Press releases and correspondence re: Youth Outreach Initiative and Gay Games.
  - Youth Media Pilot Project, ca. 2004-2006 (Box 49)
    Surveys and information about project, ITL Youth Media Conference and Community Relations projects.
- Jacqueline Gares Files, (ca. 1990s-2012, undated)
  The Jacqueline Gares Files include weekly meeting notes and minutes, holographic notes, and a small amount of episode research files, licensing agreements, and releases. There is no specific arrangement to this series.
  - American Public Television (APT) Contracts (3 folders), ca. 2010-2011 (Box 40)
    Licensing agreements. APT/EBC 2000 series XX agreement, APT/EBC 2100 series XXI agreement, APT/EBC 2200 series XXII agreement
  - APT Fall Marketplace, 2011 (Box 40)
    APT Fall Marketplace participant list.
  - Beebo Brinker Chronicles, 2007 (Box 42)
    Information regarding theatre production.
  - Bill T. Jones, 2007-2008 (Box 42)
    Articles referencing HIV positive choreographer.
  - Blank release forms (Box 40)
  - Blue State Digital - website, 2011 (Box 42)
    Correspondence and estimates regarding ITL website.
  - Board, ca. 2010-2012 (Box 41)
    Fiscal year budget and budget narrative, board meeting minutes and agendas, holographic notes, committee reports.
  - Camille Paglia and Sandra Bernhard interviews, ca. 1990s-2000s (Box 43)
  - Distribution work folder, ca. 2009-2012 (Box 40)
    Agreement between ITL and Dan Hamby Consulting.
  - Editorial (2 folders), ca. 2007-2009 (Box 43)
    Story pitches, articles. With DVD.
  - Editorial (2 folders), ca. 2011-2012 (Box 41)
    Story pitches, editorial board meeting agendas, holographic notes, series overview charts, clippings and internet articles.
  - Episode 2105 research, 2012 (Box 40)
    Episode segment outline and correspondence (HIV and the Law).
  - Episode 2107 research, undated (Box 40)
  - ESPA License Agreement, 2011 (Box 40)
    .
  - Fee for Service, undated (Box 41)
    Project budget and story pitch for ITL segment, Equality Works.
  - Florida Marriage Amendment, 2008 (Box 42)
  - Freedom 2 Marry, ca. 2008-2011 (Box 42)
  - Gay Romance Novel research, 2003-2005 (Box 42)
  - Gayhane, ca. 2007-2008 (Box 42)
    Articles and paper referencing club culture for Turkish gay and lesbian community.
  - Greenlit, undated (Box 41)
    Story pitch for ITL segment Salaam Shalom Peace.
  - Here!TV License Agreement, 2011 (Box 40)
  - In Production, ca. 2011 (Box 41)
    Voice over scripts, shot list, interview questions, and story pitch for ITL segment, In the States: New York.
  - Interns (2 folders), ca. 2005-2008 (Box 42)
    Resumes and email correspondence.
  - It's Still Elementary - Talking About Gay Issues in Schools, 2007 (Box 42)
  - ITL Blog, 2012 (Box 40)
  - JG-Personal faxes and notes (Hva, Quinn), ca. 2010-2011 (Box 40)
  - Lambda - work for hire, 2010 (Box 40)
    Work-for-hire agreements and Visions of Equality video release forms for Lambda Legal.
  - MAC AIDS, 2010 (Box 42)
    Proposals for AIDS awareness projects.
  - National Lesbian and Gay Journalist Association (NLGJA), 2011 (Box 41)
    NLGJA Convention correspondence, panels and workshop descriptions, logistical information,
  - National Producer search, 2011 (Box 42)
    With three DVDs.
  - Notebooks (2007-2012) (1 of 3) (Box 41)
    Holographic notes on notepads.
  - Notebooks (2007-2012) (2 of 3) (Box 42)
  - Notebooks (2007-2012) (3 of 3) (Box 42)
  - Performance review - Jacqueline Gares, 2010 (Box 42)
  - Post Equipment, 2011-2012 (Box 41)
    Invoices, license agreement between ITL and Channel Thirteen (13), post- media workflow plans.
  - ProdComm Meetings, 2011-2012 (Box 41)
    Marketing and communications plans.
  - Proposed Distribution Plan, 2012 (Box 40)
    In the Life Media Licensing and Digital Media Distribution Plan draft.
  - Staff & Weekly, 2011-2012 (Box 41)
    Performance reviews, internship agreement form, work plan reports, meeting agendas.
  - Stigma pt. 2 - development, 2011-2012 (Box 41)
    Transcript and episode outline, for ITL segment.
- Photographic Materials, (1993-2010, undated)
  The series includes photographs, slides, and a small amount of proof sheets and negatives. The materials represent In the Life events, including Season Premiere Galas, and individuals at the In the Life offices. Additionally, there are images of In the Life representatives advocating for the LGBT community at various events, such as the 1993 March on Washington, the 1996 Republican
  - ITL event photographs, 2000, 2009-2010 (Box 69)
    Tale of the Allergist's Wife, Pride 2010, and unidentified 2009 event.
  - ITL event photographs, 2008-2010 (Box 69)
    With proof sheets and photo discs, negatives. 2010 Gala Premiere, Pride 2010, Lana Sacks, ITL at the AIDS Memorial Quilt in Washington D.C., and unidentified 2008 event.
  - ITL Media event photographs binder, 1993, 1996, 2009-2010 (Box 69)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. With proof sheets, discs with digital images, negatives. 1996 Republican Convention, Pride 2009, 1993 March on Washington, Production shoots, office, and sets.
  - ITL Season Premiere Gala photographs, 2010 (Box 69)
    2010 Season Premiere Gala
  - Three slide boxes, undated, 1993 (Box 62)
    Unknown events. One box labeled Canada, one box labeled [Leawe's? 4-25- 1993], and one box labeled K.C.
- Office Resources, (ca. 1995-2011, undated)
  Television -- Production and direction -- Archives.; Homosexuality on television -- Archives.
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting - resource of organizations and radio and television stations (Box 47)
  - Editor Toolkit (Box 22)
    Guidelines for shooting and editing.
  - Enhancing Education: A Producer's Guide, 2002 (Box 47)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Reference guide produced by PBS for educational outreach.
  - In the Life Media - floor plans, ca. 2004 (Box 51)
  - ITL Archival Footage Rate Card, undated (Box 22)
  - ITL Intern Handbook, 2011 (Box 49)
  - ITL Personnel Handbooks, 1997-1998; 2000 (Box 51)
  - ITLM employee handbook (old), 2002 (Box 66)
    With addendums dated 2005-2006
  - LGBT Directory of Services & Resources, 2003 June (Box 35)
  - Memos regarding Post Equipment (Box 22)
    Bids and information for production equipment.
  - National Directory of LGBT Community Centers & LGBT Organizations, 2004 Nov (Box 47)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes. Directory of resources for LGBT community.
  - Post equipment receipts (Box 22)
    Receipts for technical equipment.
  - Red Book: PBS Packaging, Technical & Delivery Guidelines (photocopy) (2 folders), ca. 1995-2001 (Box 50)
  - Stock Footage Index publication, 2004 (Box 53)
    Index to specialist stock footage libraries.
  - Supervising Editor job description (Box 22)